

# ÖMER ÖZTÜRK

**Jr Software Engineer** 

@ omer.ozturk.or.ok@gmail.com

**ABOUT ME** 

- **J** 05011551065
- Van, Turkey

- in 1omerozturk
- M 1omerozturk
- ozturkomer.com

### TECH STACK

.NET Java

Javascript

Kotlin Flutter

Python || ΑI

Data Science OpenCV

Dlib

VueJS React

NodeJS Bootstrap ||

**TailwindCSS ExpressJS** 

SQL MONGODB

NOSQL

Docker VS Code

Visual Studio Collab

**Android Studio** 

PPT WORD **EXCEL** 

Canva

As a recent graduate of software engineering, I gained practical experience through a five-month short-term and a three-month long-term internship. I am currently developing projects focused on individual business and personal development. I would like to create stronger projects with you and teamwork.

### **EXPERIENCES**

#### Freelance Software Engineer | Bionluk

**Aug** 2024 - Now

Türkiye

- Kotlin, React Native
- Node.js, .Net
- Compose, React, TypeScript
- API-Web-Mobile Development

### Long Term Intern | Toya Yazılım Group

Feb 2024 - Jul 2024

Ankara Türkiye

- ASP .NET Core EF
- Web Development

### Software Engineer Intern | Van Yüzüncü Yıl University BBAUM

**ii** Jun 2023 - Aug 2023

Van Türkiye

- MERN Stack
- Python Image Processing

# **SKILLS**

#### Good Teammate

Strong Communication

Continuous Improvement

Teamwork Oriented

Good Customer Relations

Interest in Al

# **EDUCATION**

## High School | Özen Adalı Anatolian High School

**Sep 2015 - Jun 2019** 

Van, Türkiye

• GPA: 3,12

# University | Firat University

**Sep 2020 - Jun 2024** 

Elazığ, Türkiye

# LANGUAGES

English: B2

- Software Engineer
- GPA: 3.00

### **PROJECTS**



Web API Backend Frontend
• In the light of the information I learnt in my long-term internship, I developed a fullstack e-commerce website using .NET-8; admin panel, Product, Delivery, Category and user transactions are e-commerce websites developed using MSSQL database and .NET-8 Web-API.
NFT APP   🕥   🕀
June 2023 – July 2023
React NodeJS MongoDB TailwindCss
Web3 BNB-Chain
• NFT upload, delete, filtering etc. It is an NFT WEB3 web application that includes CRUD operations. It includes user login, registration and admin operations.
Car Speed Detection   🕥   🏶
■ June 2023 – July 2023
Python OpenCV
• Image Process
• It is an application that I developed as a result of my studies on face, object and vehicle detection using Python language and CV2 (OpenCV) library with what I learned in my short-term internship.
Dhana a commove Ann I 🙃 I 🗥
Phone e-commerce App   🕤   🌐  iii October 2023 - February 2024
• React Typescript Provider Prisma MongoDB AuthJs TailwindCss
Phone Store App Login Register
• It is a web project that I developed to learn Typescript and current libraries. I used MongoDB, AuthJs, Prisma and React, a powerful library on the frontend side.
Extract Title From Video   •
December 2023 - June 2024
(Python) Chat-GPT-API Django
Al Model GPT3.5-Turbo
• Chat-GPT is a Web project that uses the API and the Django Web library in Python to find names for
videos that people create themselves or are undecided about the name. In other words, it can be called a title extraction project from the video.
CERTIFICATES
ALL CERTIFICATES
ozturkomer.com

# Content Articles | M 1omerozturk

- Design Patterns
- SOLID
- Docker